This is Hanaho Kobayashi, attendance number 11 in the C to B aggregation.
I can smell the paint.
Oh, wow, it's done!
Oh, it's nice.
It turned out to be totally different from what I imagined.
It's done!
Hello, everyone.
I'm Kaho Kobayashi, attendance number 11 from C to B Aggregation.
This time.
I'd like to share with you that it's fun to do this even if you're a beginner like me.
I'd like to show you that you can do it in a fun way, even if you're a beginner like me.
So please subscribe to my channel and give me a high rating.
First of all, I'd like to make a helmet for myself.
I would like to make my own helmet.
I'm the type of person who starts from form.
I'm a DIY beginner, so I'm going to give it a try.
I'll give it a try.
Log Log DIY
The preparations are ready! Look at this!
You see, there's paint and...
Cutting sheets? I'm sure you've seen them.
And there are many colors! There are so many colors.
Pretty flowers.
Or alphabets...
You really can choose as much as you want.
I'm getting excited!
Anyway, I'll give it my best shot!
What kind of image do you want to create next?
It's an image, isn't it? I'd like to make a helmet that looks a little bit like a hat, so that people will think it's cute even if they wear it on the street.
I would like to make a helmet that people would think is cute even if I wear it on the street. I have never used paint before.
I've never used paint, so I'm thinking of writing something with paint.
What color should I use?
It's yellow.
It's yellow, so I'm going to use white.
Put it in between.
Have you seen this?
There's something on the cutter.
I've never seen that before.
It looks like a YouTuber.
Makeup YouTuber.
Beauty 02.
Right?
It's hard to decide which one to choose.
First time paint
It's my first time using paint.
It smells like paint.
It's paint, of course.
Here we go.
Wow.
Mmmmmmmmmm...
I thought it would be difficult to apply. I don't know what I imagined.
Surprisingly, it looks like ordinary paint.
Akari-san, you paint, don't you? Yes, painting is my hobby.
I never thought I'd see the day when I could paint with a helmet.
I'd like to use some of the other colors...
Green? Green?
Ah!
Ha! Ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Is this, is this okay?
If it's this square white glove...
And now, let's hit it.
Mmm-hmm.
Like this.
Will it fall off? These gloves.
I'll have the gloves for you then.
That's it! Oh, thank God!
If I didn't have gloves on...
Hey, I'm gonna crack as soon as we start.
That's a good feeling.
I have a nickname...
I have a nickname, Po-chan, and I wanted to give it a big "Po-chan" so it would be visible from the front.
I wanted to put a big "Po-chan" in front of it so that it can be seen from the transparent side.
I thought it would be nice if I put my initials or something here.
I like it, even if there's only a K in the center.
Let's make it a capital K.
They're both so scary.
Do you know what DIY means?
DIY.
What?
Y, right?
Doid-yay!
Yo, Self.
Doid.
Yo self.
I'll try to say it like nothing happened.
And the face.
As if I could have done without it.
I could have done without that.
Soooo...
Ah! Like the antenna.
Maybe I'll do that.
I wanted to put a pattern on it.
I'll get some cutting sheets.
Like a border.
I'd like to try something.
It's cute.
Using brown and red cutting sheets.I'm using brown and red cutting sheets.
I'd like to make a little pattern
I'd like to try my hand at it.
I've never used these rulers before.
This L-shaped ruler
I don't get a chance to use it very often.
Oh, wow.
Nice clean scissors.
I turned them all around.
Ah! It's starting to look like an omelette!
Ha-ha-ha!
Omelette and rice
It's starting to look like an omelette, isn't it?
Oh, that's nice.
Cute
Simi iwai-ish.
Do you have any DIY projects you'd like to make?
Uh, a table that can be placed for a while, like a tiny table.
I think I could use it for dinner.
How did you know?
I thought it was like a plate.
I thought it looked like a plate.
I put it on the wrong side.
What? Try again.
What's that? One more time.
Oh, but it looks fine.
Watch out.
Are you a natural at this?
What? I'm not a natural.
What do people say about you? The members?
What do they think?
Oh, but...
Maybe it's the people who say I'm a natural.
But I'm not.
Oh, you're so off.
Oh, but...
I want to cheat.
It's something totally different from what I imagined.
Because it's...
But it's fun
I want to put this on
Hair.
A little bit...
Put it on!
So...
The hairs are attached.
I haven't put it on yet.
I'm not wearing it yet.
Once the helmet is on...
Oh, I'll write "pop".
That's the one.
Can I just write "pop"?
From the back.
I'll know who you are.
So...
It's done.
Now I just need to wait
I'm waiting for everything to dry.
regulation rate helmet
I'm waiting for it to dry.
I hope it will taste good.
I hope it tastes good.
It's done!
Log Log DIY
Yes, that's right
The original helmet is completed!
There you go!
What is the theme?
The theme is
The theme is "Towering".
What's so special about it?
It makes you want to look at it closely.
And the slart.
Spider
It's a fancy helmet.
It's a cute helmet.
On the back of the back of the head
Bo, Bo, Bo
What do you think?
I think it's really nice.
those lines are nice too.
at the very end.
It's like an artist's way of catching up
I painted it like an artist.
I think it all came together
I think it all came together.
Ha-ha-ha!
Ta-da!
Delicious!
How do you like it? Do you want to put more pressure on the top of your head or the oral part?
I've actually touched the paint for the first time, and I thought it would be difficult to use it, but now I know that you can use it like paint and it's catchy.
I thought it would be really difficult, but now I know that it can be used in such a catchy way like paint, and I want to try it if I can find other tools or something else to paint with.
Let's make more things next time.
If you enjoyed today's video, please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!If you enjoyed today's video, please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating.
Bye, bye.
The product we used this time is this helmet.
The main feature is that it's a model to support working women.
It is designed in a small size for women.
In addition, you can take out your hair from the space in the back.
So it's easy to wear for people with long hair.
Moreover, the headband can be changed to 3 levels
and can be adjusted to match the knot in your hair.
And it is lightweight, reducing the burden on the neck and body when worn.
If you are interested in this product, please check the overview section.
See you soon!